# COSTANDINO ELEFTHERIADIS

# SOFTWARE ENGINEER

#### CONTACT

(+27) 83 262 5020

dinoelef@gmail.com

dinothedeveloper.github.io

in dino-eleftheriadis

Johannesburg, South Africa

# **KEY SKILLS**

- React
- Angular
- · JavaScript & TypeScript
- HTML & CSS
- C#
- SQL
- Kubernetes
- Docker
- · Octopus Deploy
- SonarQube
- Azure
- Kibana

#### **EDUCATION**

Jan - Dec 2021 - 2021 ~ University of Pretoria

BACHELOR OF INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY HONOURS IN INFORMATION SYSTEMS.

Jan - Dec 2018 - 2020 ~ IIE Varsity College Sandton

BACHELOR OF COMPUTER AND INFORMATION SCIENCES (Qualified with distinction).

# LANGUAGE

English: Fluent (Read, Write and Speak) Greek: Satisfactory (Speak and Read) Afrikaans: Satisfactory (Read and Write)

#### NATIONALITY

South African Greek (EU Passport & Citizenship)

#### **ABOUT ME**

I am a software engineer with two years of working experience. I possess an innate passion for continuous learning, unparalleled teamwork abilities, and a proven history of consistently delivering exceptional outcomes. I approach tasks with meticulous organisation and unwavering motivation, striving to achieve optimal results. Moreover, my remarkable entrepreneurial spirit and determination drive me to actively contribute to the growth and development of businesses.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

# Front-End Web Developer & UX Specialist

June - Present 2023 - Present

Bettabets

As the Lead Frontend Developer and UX Specialist at Bettabets, I've
transformed the online casino to a whole new level, creating an eye-catching
and intuitive user experience. Through the use of A/B testing, heatmaps, user
recordings, and other data analytics, I've optimized functionality and
engagement as well as leading a major increase in efficiency. My innovative
approach has not only revamped the platform but also positioned Bettabets as a
leader in online casino design, showcasing my prowess in frontend development
and UX enhancement.

# **Junior Software Engineer**

Jan - Jan 2022 - 2023

Paycorp payment services

- I took on an early role as a team-lead and managed various developers below
  me. In my role, I exhibited excellent communication skills, goal-setting, strategyplanning, and organisational skills. I worked on developing a web application
  that assisted the finance department to monitor and pay merchants who own
  self-cashing ATMs. I also worked on smaller projects for other departments
  within the company.
- I maintained frequent and meaningful interactions with the group Chief Information Officer and other esteemed senior leaders within the organisation.
   Additionally, I took on the responsibility of delivering regular presentations to these executives, and providing comprehensive project updates.

# **Freelance Developer**

Jan - Present 2022 - Present

I worked as a website developer on a freelance basis. During my leisure time, I
dedicated myself to freelance development projects. In this capacity, I
collaborated with clients to define project requirements, identify target
audiences, and troubleshoot any encountered issues. My goal was to deliver
optimal website solutions tailored to the specific needs of the client base